<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour of San Francisco</string>

    <string name="GGPTitle">"Golden Gate Park"</string>
    <string name="Golden_Gate_Park">"Golden Gate Park, located in San Francisco, California, United States, is a large urban park consisting of 1,017 acres of public grounds. It is administered by the San Francisco Recreation and Parks Department, which began in 1871 to oversee the development of Golden Gate Park." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="FMWTitle">"Fisherman's Wharf"</string>
    <string name="FisherMansWharf">"Fisherman's Wharf is a neighborhood and popular tourist attraction in San Francisco, California. It roughly encompasses the northern waterfront area of San Francisco from Ghirardelli Square or Van Ness Avenue east to Pier 35 or Kearny Street. The F Market streetcar runs through the area, the Powell-Hyde cable car lines runs to Aquatic Park, at the edge of Fisherman's Wharf, and the Powell-Mason cable car line runs a few blocks away." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="GGBTitle">"Golden Gate Bridge"</string>
    <string name="GGB">"The Golden Gate Bridge is a suspension bridge spanning the Golden Gate strait, the one-mile-wide (1.6 km), three-mile-long (4.8 km) channel between San Francisco Bay and the Pacific Ocean. The structure links the American city of San Francisco, California – the northern tip of the San Francisco Peninsula – to Marin County, carrying both U.S. Route 101 and California State Route 1 across the strait. The bridge is one of the most internationally recognized symbols of San Francisco, California, and the United States. It has been declared one of the Wonders of the Modern World by the American Society of Civil Engineers." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="CTTitle">"China Town"</string>
    <string name="ChinaTown">"The Chinatown centered on Grant Avenue and Stockton Street in San Francisco, California, (Chinese: 唐人街; pinyin: tángrénjiē; Jyutping: tong4 jan4 gaai1) is the oldest Chinatown in North America and the largest Chinese community outside Asia. It is the oldest of the four notable Chinatowns in the city. Since its establishment in 1848, it has been highly important and influential in the history and culture of ethnic Chinese immigrants in North America. Chinatown is an enclave that continues to retain its own customs, languages, places of worship, social clubs, and identity. There are two hospitals, numerous parks and squares, a post office, and other infrastructure. While recent immigrants and the elderly choose to live in here because of the availability of affordable housing and their familiarity with the culture, the place is also a major tourist attraction, drawing more visitors annually than the Golden Gate Bridge." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="ATitle">"Alcatraz Island"</string>
    <string name="Alcatraz">"Alcatraz Island is located in the San Francisco Bay, 1.25 miles (2.01 km) offshore from San Francisco, California, United States. The small island was developed with facilities for a lighthouse, a military fortification, a military prison (1868), and a federal prison from 1933 until 1963. Beginning in November 1969, the island was occupied for more than 19 months by a group of aboriginal people from San Francisco who were part of a wave of Native activism across the nation with public protests through the 1970s. In 1972, Alcatraz became a national recreation area and received designation as a National Historic Landmark in 1986." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="AAMTitle">"Asian Art Museum"</string>
    <string name="AAM">"The Asian Art Museum of San Francisco houses one of the most comprehensive Asian art collections in the world, with more than 18,000 works of art in its permanent collection, some as much as 6,000 years old." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="SFMOMATitle">"San Francisco Museum of Modern Art"</string>
    <string name="SFMOMA">"The San Francisco Museum of Modern Art (SFMOMA) is a modern art museum located in San Francisco, California. A nonprofit organization, SFMOMA holds an internationally recognized collection of modern and contemporary art, and was the first museum on the West Coast devoted solely to 20th-century art. The museum’s current collection includes over 33,000 works of painting, sculpture, photography, architecture, design, and media arts. They are displayed in 170,000 square feet (16,000 m2) of exhibition space, making the museum one of the largest in the United States overall, and one of the largest in the world for modern and contemporary art." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="OBTitle">"Ocean Beach"</string>
    <string name="OceanBeach">"Ocean Beach is a beach on the west coast of San Francisco, California, United States, bordering the Pacific Ocean. It is adjacent to Golden Gate Park, the Richmond District, and the Sunset District. The Great Highway runs alongside the beach, and the Cliff House and the site of the former Sutro Baths sit at the northern end. The beach is a part of the Golden Gate National Recreation Area, which is administered by the National Park Service." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="BBTitle">"Baker Beach"</string>
    <string name="BakerBeach">"Baker Beach is a public beach on the peninsula of San Francisco, California, U.S.A.     The beach lies on the shore of the Pacific Ocean in the northwest of the city. It is roughly a half mile (800 m) long, beginning just south of Golden Gate Point (where the Golden Gate Bridge connects with the peninsula), extending southward toward the Seacliff peninsula, the Palace of the Legion of Honor and the Sutro Baths. The northern section of Baker Beach is "frequented by clothing-optional sunbathers". As such it is considered a nude beach." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="GSTitle">"Ghirardelli Square"</string>
    <string name="GhirardelliSquare">"Ghirardelli Square is a landmark public square with shops and restaurants in the Fisherman's Wharf area of San Francisco, California. A portion of the area was listed on the National Register of Historic Places in 1982 as Pioneer Woolen Mills and D. Ghirardelli Company.The square once featured over 40 specialty shops and restaurants. Some of the original shops and restaurants still occupy the square." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="P39Title">"Pier 39"</string>
    <string name="Pier39">"Pier 39 is a shopping center and popular tourist attraction built on a pier in San Francisco, California. At Pier 39, there are shops, restaurants, a video arcade, street performances, the Aquarium of the Bay, virtual 3D rides, and views of California sea lions hauled out on docks on Pier 39's marina. The marina is also home to the floating Forbes Island restaurant. A two-story carousel is one of the pier's more dominant features, although it is not directly visible from the street and sits towards the end of the pier. The family-oriented entertainment and presence of marine mammals make this a popular tourist location for families with kids." - Wikipedia</string>

    <string name="APTitle">"Als Place"</string>
    <string name="AlsPlace">Als Place has a rating of 4.7 stars out of 5 on Google Reviews and is an American Restaurant.</string>

    <string name="LTTitle">"La Taqueria"</string>
    <string name="LaTaqueria">La Taqueria has a rating of 4.4 stars out of 5 on Google Reviews and is a Mexican Restaurant.</string>

    <string name="FWTitle">"Flour + Water"</string>
    <string name="FAndW">Flour and Water has a rating of 4.3 stars out of 5 on Google Reviews and is an Italian Restaurant.</string>
</resources>